http://www.twpsin.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Search form
Search
About Us
Our HistoryVision & MissionMD MessageDNPCareerCorporate Social ResponsibilityNews & Events
Printing Products
Book PrintingChildren's BooksIllustrated BooksSpecialty BooksBoard BooksLoose Leaf Books
Commercial PrintingAnnual ReportsSales CollateralsPrint on Demand
Card PrintingTCG CardsCollector’s CardsCommercial CardsCard PackagingAccessories
Why TWP
Our HistoryCertificationsFacility MachineryIntellectual PropertyUnder One Roof PrintingCorporate Social Responsibility
Information Collected by TWP
TWP collects your information when you register on our site, fill out our forms or provided to us in any other ways.
When registering on our site or filling out a form, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You can withhold certain information pertaining to you and visit our site anonymously, but this may limit the accessibility and functionalities of our services.
TWP will only retain the personal information you have supplied for as long as is necessary to achieve the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and in line with its data retention guidelines.
Information Usage
Any information that TWP has collected will be used in the following ways:
To create personalized experience for you.
To improve our website.
To improve customer service.
To send periodic emails with TWP related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.
The email address you have provided may be used to send you information, respond to enquiries or for any other request or questions.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while the user is browsing the site.
The TWP website uses cookies to understand your preference and save them for future visits.
Securing Your Information
Your TWP account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your account by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.
TWP follows the guidelines and standards provided by the ‘Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (PDPA)’ which is governed by the Personal Data Protection Commission of Singapore. PDPA establishes a data protection law that comprises various rules governing the collection, use, disclosure and care of personal data. It recognizes both the rights of individuals to protect their personal data, including rights of access and correction, and the needs of organizations to collect, use or disclose personal data for legitimate and reasonable purposes.
Sharing of Information
TWP will not sell, trade or distribute your personal information to outside parties. This however does not include trusted third parties who may assist in operating our website, conduct our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep your information confidential.
We may also release your personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of TWP, our employees, our users or others.
Removal of Personal Information
If you wish to have your account deleted and/or personal information removed from our database, please write in a written request to our email twpsg@twpsin.com.
Information Affected by This Policy
The information affected by this policy is only limited to information collected by TWP online and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes
TWP reserves the rights to revise our privacy policy from time-to-time. Revised privacy policy will apply to the use of this website from the date of publication of the revised terms of service on this website. You shall be responsible for reviewing and becoming familiar with any such modification. Continued usage of this website will constitute as your acceptance of the terms as modified. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.
Last updated: 29th June 2014
Terms of ServicePrivacy PolicySitemap
Get a Quote
FAQ
Feedback
Book PrintingCommercial PrintingTrading Card PrintingStationery PrintingPackaging PrintingCustomer Support
